

# **GUIDO** CALCIANO

WEB DEVELOPER

## PERFIL PROFESIONAL

I've been working with groups and teams for the last 10 years, always fully committed with the task. After giving my first steps into IT, I'm excited to keep on learning and improving every day. I'm reliable and responsible, adaptable and great at teamwork. I'm currently looking for oportunities to develop my full potential and bring all my aptitudes and knowledge to a new project!

## PROYECTOS



Portfolio



Fotografiando: Travel and Photography Website. HTML5, CSS,

Javascript and Bootstrap.



😝 Road Trip Simulator:

Text-based adventure game. Currently in development with Python. Play it!

## CONTACT

**(1)** 11 5732 4784

O CABA, Buenos Aires, Argentina

() /guidocano

in /guidocalciano

# **EDUCATION**

## CODO A CODO 4.0 - FULLSTACK PYTHON.

Buenos Aires City Goverment. Aug 2021 - Dec 2021.

HTML, CSS, Javascript, Python, Bootstrap, Diseño Web, Vue, MySQL, Flask, among others. Learnt how to fluently use different programming languages and the ability to develop different kinds of Websites.

#### **BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN PSYCHOLOGY.**

Buenos Aires University. Mar 2006 - Dec 2012.

In my bachelor's Degree I acquired a practical and at the same time complex view of different problems and situations. As well as the capability to listen and to understand different points of view, allowing me to arrive to consense.

## EXPERIENCE

#### SPECIAL EDUCATION TEACHER.

Adeei. Mar 2018 - Dec 2021.

Working with children and teenagers I developed my ability to learn, communicate and teach in an easy and didactic way. I worked in collaboration with other professionals to achieve the best interests of each student.

#### ASESOR PARLAMENTARIO.

Buenos Aires City Legislature. Jan 2016 - Dec 2017.

Working in making and correcting law projects, organization of events and schedule, communication with different areas and parliamentary representatives.

# SKILLS

### **TECHNOLOGIES**

- PYTHON
- JAVASCRIPT
- HTML
- CSS
- BOOTSTRAP
- MYSQL

## **SOFT SKILLS**

**LANGUAGES** 

SPANISH: native.

• ENGLISH: bilingual.

CEFR level: C1 (IELTS)

PROBLEM-SOLVER CREATIVITY ADAPTABILITY TEAMWORK RESPONSABILITY AND COMMITMENT CRITICAL THINKING OPEN-MINDEDNESS COMMUNICATION SELF-MOTIVATION